You can't choose your family but she can.
The Perfect Teacher is a tv movie, thriller film directed by Jim Donovan.
A spoiled, selfish teenager becomes infatuated with her teacher.
She befriends his daughter as a way of worming her way into the family,
and sets about manipulating every aspect of his life.
Devon, played by Megan Park.
Jim Wilkes, played by David Charvet.
Rachel, played by Boti Bliss.
Annique Wilkes, played by Keeva Lynk.
Kinsey Ray, played by Amanda Tilson.
Monica, played by Kimberly-Sue Murray.
Kathryn Love Newton (born February 8, 1997) is an American actress.
She is known for her starring roles as Louise Brooks in the CBS comedy series Gary Unmarried (2008–2010), Abigail Carlson in the HBO
mystery drama series Big Little Lies (2017–2019), and Allie Pressman in the Netflix teen drama series The Society (2019).
She is also known for portraying the older versions of Claire Novak in The CW dark fantasy series Supernatural
(2014–2018) and Joanie Clark in the AMC period drama series Halt and Catch Fire (2016–2017).
Newton has appeared in various films, including Bad Teacher (2011), Three Billboards Outside Ebbing, Missouri (2017), Blockers (2018), Pokémon
Detective Pikachu (2019), Freaky (2020), The Map of Tiny Perfect Things (2021), Ant-Man and the Wasp: Quantumania (2023), and Abigail (2024).
For her role in the horror film Paranormal Activity 4 (2012), Newton received the
Young Artist Award for Best Leading Young Actress in a Feature Film.
The film explores themes of love triangle, teacher,
teenage girl, teacher student relationship.
The tone is intense.